<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[685]]></id><name><![CDATA[productmedia]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Media (Audio / Video)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Videos & Music]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Enrich your product descriptions with explanatory videos and video or audio previews!  The Product Media module lets you import your own media content (audio and video files) and easily add it to your]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/videos-music/685-product-media-audio-video.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/685.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Enrich your product descriptions with explanatory videos and video or audio previews!  The Product Media module lets you import your own media content (audio and video files) and easily add it to your product pages.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Make your product pages more interactive and your products more accessibleGive more information on your products: benefits, a better description, recommendations for use, etc.Easily increase your conversion rateBoost your sales and reduce the return rate of your products]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/611425-pprod/product-media-audio-video.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/611425-pbig/product-media-audio-video.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5 - Create ​​bundles of products]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Cross-selling & Product Bundles]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/cross-selling-product-bundles/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Allow the purchase of combinations of products with or without a discount, in one click  Would you like to increase your average shopping cart and at the same time, allow your customers to save money if they purchase several products simultaneously? It is now possible thanks to&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;!  Without waiting any longer, you can create packs of products that can be purchased in one click, without worrying about stock or their combinations.  A precious additional sales tool  Accompany your customers in their buying process, by offering them&nbsp;packs of coherent products&nbsp;that you will have predefined, just as the salesman in a real shop would do. Such as for example: this fantastic camera, memory card and tripod. You know that this selection is appropriate and that it will appeal to your customers.  Or you could even use your best-sellers, by adding them to those that are less visible, to allow your customers to discover them.  Your packs will need to be made up of 2 products minimum, the number is unlimited. Push the quantity per product, choose the combinations of your choice, there are multiple options allowing you to multiply the possibilities.  Would you like to reserve the purchase of a product within a pack? That is also possible! You will therefore be able&nbsp;to offer a free product&nbsp;if it is purchased as part of a pack. The possibilities are infinite!  Integrated assistant  It isn&#39;t always obvious deciding which products should be offered within a pack. Here again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution to the problem. When creating your pack, our module will supply you with strategic information, like the number of products sold or their available stock. There is also an integrated&nbsp;dynamic price simulator&nbsp;for your pack, to help you see more clearly when creating your business transaction, without you harming your profit margin.  Remain the maestro of combinations  One of the products that you have added to your pack is available in several colors, but you don&#39;t want to offer them all in this set? Advanced Pack&nbsp;will allow you to do this.  You will also have the possibility of predefining a combination by default, for each of the products of your pack, even if it&#39;s different to the one defined in your catalog.  Your customers will then be able to&nbsp;personalise their selection&nbsp;amongst the characteristics that you will have chosen to integrate in the offer.  Business Incentive  Incentive is something that motivates your visitor to make a purchase The main aim is to convince more of your site visitors to finish their order and/or&nbsp;spend more money per transaction. Perhaps you have already tried, by offering free delivery over a certain amount of purchases, or to offer discounts on certain products or even to send discount vouchers? All of these methods work, but their range is limited, as these promotions are usually temporary due to their excessive cost! Stop looking, you have already found the solution !  To entice your customers,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will give you the choice of applying a discount when all the products in the shopping cart are ordered, thus encouraging the purchase of the whole pack.  3 possibilities are available:&nbsp;Offer a specific discount on&nbsp;each product&nbsp;in the packApply a general discount on&nbsp;the set of productsApply a&nbsp;fixed price, such as a psychological price, for example Advanced Pack&nbsp;will also be able to manage the discounts already applied to your products, allowing you to integrate them in the pack price, or on the contrary, to exclude them, in order to choose the predefined discount on the pack. This decision will be made even easier thanks to our&nbsp;clear and clean-looking interface, that will allow you to see the discounted products very easily.  You won&#39;t need to worry about the coherence of your prices anymore  Have you ever had to review all the prices in your catalog, to detect any possible incoherences and correct them? What would happen if you had to manually manage the repercussions of these changes in product pricing in your packs? This would represent a significant extra workload if if it&#39;s not anticipated within the choice of management solutions within your packs!  Once again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution.  By default, in the case where no reduction has been applied, the pack price is the sum of the products making it up. Should you need to modify the price of a product after having created the pack,&nbsp;the pack price will automatically be updated, and without you having to intervene.  In those cases where you will apply a discount to one or more products in an existing pack, and on condition you have authorized the&nbsp;promotional implications, the pack price will also be changed, showing your customers the discount that has been applied.  Is one of the products of your pack subject to an green-tax? No problem, it will automatically be reflected in the pack price and will be clearly stated, guaranteeing absolute&nbsp;respect for the legislation.  Regarding the management of your stock, everything has been automated!  For each pack ordered, the product stocks it contains will be&nbsp;automatically deducted. This way you will avoid the double management of stock or the frustration generated by sales rendered impossible, due to the bad assignation of quantities. Also, in the case where a product in a pack is out of stock, it will&nbsp;automatically be displayed as unavailable&nbsp;for purchase thanks to an availability warning system that is both elegant and modern.  For your customers, we have integrated a graphic and fun notification system, allowing the instant identification of stock shortages on combinations or products making up the pack.&nbsp;There&#39;s no chance of you receiving orders for products that are out of stock !  Highlight your packs and sell more  Once you have defined your pack, you will be able to configure it in the same way as you would a classic product. Everything is possible, such as assigning it customized images, classing it in the category of your choice,&nbsp;optimizing your SEO, writing a customized description, attributing it an EAN code or a specific reference, configuring its volume to calculate delivery costs, etc...  For those that are pressed for time, and in order to facilitate their marketing,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will automatically display all the photos of the products that make it up, as well as their descriptions, in the form of tabs. Your customers will be correctly informed, without leaving the page of your pack, and&nbsp;able to finalise their purchase in one click.  And that&#39;s not all... For more visibility, your packs will automatically be&nbsp;highlighted on their data sheets&nbsp;for those being sold in lots This way, you will encourage your customers to order the pack, rather than the product they were initially interested in. Essentially, this is&nbsp;cross-selling: an accessible method of&nbsp;increasing your average shopping cart&nbsp;!  We don&#39;t forget designers  From the beginning, we have integrated the fact that this module should be easily adapted by your web agency or designer/integrator. The module adapts itself perfectly to the default PrestaShop 1.5 and 1.6 themes, whilst allowing the most advanced graphic personalization.  A set of JavaScript templates and CSS style sheets are delivered as models with the module,&nbsp;to facilitate the integration process. Either yourself or your integrator will therefore be able to use all of the functionalities of the&nbsp;Advanced Pack 5&nbsp;engine, in order to present them in the graphic form that will best correspond with the general atmosphere of your online store.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[289.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[224.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pprod/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pbig/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1048]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookpsshoptab]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Shop for Fan Page]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Products on Facebook & Social Networks]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create a multilingual and completely customized Facebook shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/products-on-facebook-social-networks/1048-advanced-shop-for-fan-page.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1048.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create a multilingual and completely customized Facebook shop]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[* * * WINNER OF THE 2011 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE * * * Stand out from the competition and present your products on Facebook in a completely customized shop tab that will differ from the shop tab natively offered by Facebook and used by many merchants.(x) Effective way to increase your sales, the "Facebook shop" has become essential in the e-commerce area. It allows you to display your products in sale on your site directly on the most popular social network. Then, you make the most of your Facebook community to boost the traffic on your PrestaShop site. Natively, Facebook gives you the opportunity to add a "shop" section to your page where you can present your products. However, you are obliged to comply with the design and navigation features imposed by Facebook. You do not have the opportunity to make your shop really unique. Moreover, this tab can only be displayed in one language and product prices are only visible in one currency. Contrary to the native shop tab, the "Advanced Shop for Fan Page" module allows you to: create a&nbsp;completely customized&nbsp;Facebook shop, whether in terms of design, menu type or displaycreate a&nbsp;multilingual and multicurrency&nbsp;shopnot need to submit your products to Facebook for review&nbsp;in order to make them visible for the publicmake the PrestaShop website's modifications&nbsp;instantly visible&nbsp;on the Facebook shop (changes of price, product image,...)display&nbsp;featured categories&nbsp;on the home pagedisplay on Facebook&nbsp;the average rating&nbsp;of each product/category, given on your site (with the shape of stars) if you also have installed on your Prestashop our product rating "Customer Ratings and Reviews Pro + Google Rich Snippets" module (available here:&nbsp;https://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/6144-customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.html)  Notes: (x) 1/ So that real-time harmonization between Facebook and your online store is possible, the module has to create a new custom "shop" tab,&nbsp;independent of the default "shop" tab already installed by Facebook&nbsp;on your page. 2/ if you want to create&nbsp;Facebook catalogs and tag your products on Facebook and Instagram,&nbsp;you should choose our&nbsp;"Dynamic Ads + Pixel"&nbsp;module instead, that is available here:&nbsp;https://addons.prestashop.com/en/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/23671-dynamic-ads-pixel.html. 3/ Facebook mobile app&nbsp;does not allow custom tabs insertion,&nbsp;like the one created by our module. Therefore, this latter can&nbsp;only&nbsp;be displayed on the Facebook web version. If you want to see your Facebook shop on mobile, you have to choose our "Dynamic Ads + Pixel" module (available here:&nbsp;https://addons.prestashop.com/en/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/23671-dynamic-ads-pixel.html) in order to import your products into the native Facebook shop tab (however you will not be able to customize the shop).  To know more about the difference between the Facebook native shop tab (and filled by our "Dynamic Ads + Pixel" module) and the custom tab set by our "Advanced Shop for Fan Page" module, read our detailed comparison at this address: https://faq.businesstech.fr/en/faq/230&nbsp; ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[94.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963149-pprod/advanced-shop-for-fan-page.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963149-pbig/advanced-shop-for-fan-page.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstrackingv2]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Delivery Tracking]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Do you deliver with UPS, a company known for its speed and reliability?  With the UPS Tracking module, make your life even easier by tracking your UPS shipments directly from your Back-Office and impr]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/delivery-tracking/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Do you deliver with UPS, a company known for its speed and reliability?  With the UPS Tracking module, make your life even easier by tracking your UPS shipments directly from your Back-Office and improve customer&rsquo;s satisfaction by automatically sending update emails to your clients when their order status has changed.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Take advantage of the UPS Tracking module: &nbsp;Get advanced tracking for your shipments, step by step, straight from your Back OfficeImprove your customers&rsquo; overall purchasing experience by regularly informing them about their order status and delivery of their package&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611439-pprod/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611439-pbig/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1768]]></id><name><![CDATA[gmerchantcenter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Merchant Center (Google Shopping)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Price Comparison]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/price-comparison/1768-google-merchant-center-google-shopping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1768.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop. The performance of Google AdWords Shopping campaigns and your presence in the "Shopping" results of Google's search engine largely depends on the quality of your Google Merchant Center feed and completeness of your data. The more information accurate you include, the better the results ! This very complete module will let you achieve just that and maximize your chances of obtaining good rankings on Google Shopping, while minimizing the time you will need to spend to have all your products accepted by Google. Instantly boost your traffic : Google Shopping and AdWords benefit from hundreds of millions of hits each month. Moreover this traffic is highly targeted and brings qualified visitors to your shop Increase your sales and ROI : Because traffic is extremely targeted, Google Shopping and Google AdWords Shopping Campaigns provide you with one of the highest return on investment rates compared to other marketing channels and is very cost effective About your products export, the power of the module allows you to only focus on the configuration of a single product feed (a primary feed) and not to waste time with the configuration of "supplemental feeds" and numerous "rules" provided by Google. You modify your product information directly in the module and you have the possibility to automate the update of all your data in Google Shopping, daily. Present in over 37 countries as of today, Google Shopping is a fast track start for international expansion  With more than 6000 copies sold, 510+ reviews and an average 4.7/5 rating, our Google Merchant Center (Google Shopping) module is hands down the most robust, accurate, powerful and complete module for Google Shopping. We also have extensive knowledge and experience on the ins and outs of Google's rather complex requirements, and our tech support team will gladly help answer your questions to the best of their ability !   For power users and SEM agencies, for even more great features, including advanced custom labels management, promotions feed and quick inventory feed, you may be interested in purchasing the PRO version of the module available on https://addons.prestashop.com/en/price-comparison/20908-google-merchant-center-pro-google-shopping.html  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed ! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.7.14]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.4.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963144-pprod/google-merchant-center-google-shopping.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963144-pbig/google-merchant-center-google-shopping.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2072]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedtopmenu]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu - Responsive]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Menu]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Discover and choose the most popular and more powerful responsive mega menu for PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/menu/2072-advanced-top-menu-responsive.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2072.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Discover and choose the most popular and more powerful responsive mega menu for PrestaShop]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu allows you to build all types of horizontal navigation bars: single bar, drop-down menus, rich menu, mega-menu with columns. Advanced Top Menu is a PrestaShop Addon that will help you to simplify the navigation and usability of your website. Give to your visitors an overwiew of your catalog making them to quickly find the desired product. Thanks to its highly modular design, you will be able to use your menu bar to display images, promotions or advertisements, and put forward your offers and services that make your store unique. With a rich configuration interface, it makes you able to customize your menu bar without special technical knowledge:ResponsiveUnlimited number of tabsUnlimited number of columnsUnlimited number of elementsSimple and complete graphical customizationAutomatic menu generation from your catalogAll content types supported: categories, manufacturers, suppliers, CMS, custom links...Conditional display depending on the status of your visitor A faster and cleaner configuration interfaceNew default theme for optimal design out of the boxNew appearance settingsNew specific settings for mobileA Sticky mode, which let your menu always visible regardless of scroller positionAllows you to restrict the display of some elements for desktop or mobile viewAllows you to add different images for each languageOpening animation effect on submenusDelay on opening submenusContextual help tips in Back Office]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.12.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573526-pprod/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573526-pbig/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2376]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestagiftvouchers]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Loyalty Coupons / Discount vouchers after purchase]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Referral & Loyalty Programs]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Build customer loyalty by offering discount vouchers for future purchases!  Comprehensive and easy to configure, this module will enable you to create discount vouchers and send them to your customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/referral-loyalty-programs/2376-loyalty-coupons-discount-vouchers-after-purchase.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2376.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Build customer loyalty by offering discount vouchers for future purchases!  Comprehensive and easy to configure, this module will enable you to create discount vouchers and send them to your customers automatically if they have their account logged in and they&#39;ve placed a certain type of order: minimum amount, specific product, product from a particular category... the choice is yours, to be made based on your needs !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Loyalty&nbsp;Discount Vouchers module you can:  &nbsp;Automatically create cart rules that generate offer codes emailed to your customers,&nbsp;Customize the coupons&rsquo; name, their value as a percentage or amount as well as their validity period,&nbsp;Increase average cart size on your site by defining minimum purchase amounts in order to use the discount voucher,&nbsp;Build customer loyalty by encouraging customers to buy again from your store,&nbsp;Easily liquidate your inventory of products of your choice, and better promote your new products and categories]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[49.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708607-pprod/loyalty-coupons-discount-vouchers-after-purchase.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708607-pbig/loyalty-coupons-discount-vouchers-after-purchase.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplaces]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best-seller and exclusive on PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplaces/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best-seller and exclusive on PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can easily integrate your PrestaShop store to the world&rsquo;s top marketplace and significantly increase your sales. You import your orders into your PrestaShop store and centralize your stocks.  Managing your inventory efficiently and quickly honoring your Amazon orders allows you to increase the degree of customer satisfaction and thus automatically increase the rank of your seller performance.  The design of the module is based on the initial experience of online retailers. The module was developed by an online retailer for the service of his colleagues and it was developed by a team of professional developers, by making it easy to use and to have the maximum efficiency.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support that is provided unconditionally until the products are placed online and the first orders are imported.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons&nbsp; since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.4.094]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[229.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/686436-pprod/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/686436-pbig/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2659]]></id><name><![CDATA[protectmyshop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Protect My Shop / Protéger Ma Boutique]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Security & Access]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module developped by LIBRASOFT gives you the best protection for your shop against thiefs and hackers. You can parameter in your back office up to 9 scripts of protection]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/website-security-access/2659-protect-my-shop-proteger-ma-boutique.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2659.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module developped by LIBRASOFT gives you the best protection for your shop against thiefs and hackers. You can parameter in your back office up to 9 scripts of protection. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module developped by LIBRASOFT gives you the best protection for your shop against thiefs and hackers. You can parameter in your back office 9 scripts of protection. &nbsp; In the back-office of the module, you can activate / unactivate one by one the protection scripts. The protection is totally personalizable, activating or not some protections, but even some specific rules of these&nbsp;protections.  You will be protected against all types of injection :SQL InjectionsXSS InjectionsSHELL Commands InjectionsCode InjectionsCGI Injections You will be protected against data thief :Hotlinking protectionFiles protectionCopy-Paste protectionRight Clic protection No surprise, you can adapt the protections to your needs easily through the multiples available tabs of personalisation. &nbsp; Your shop protection has no price. Protect My Shop Module is the better protection module ever developped for PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668741-pprod/protect-my-shop-proteger-ma-boutique.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668741-pbig/protect-my-shop-proteger-ma-boutique.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2778]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedsearch4]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Search 4]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Search & Filters]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The best and more popular layered navigation module available for PrestaShop ! Best Module Award winner]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/search-filters/2778-advanced-search-4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2778.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The best and more popular layered navigation module available for PrestaShop ! Best Module Award winner.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[An essential tool for shops offering a vast selection of products, Advanced Search 4 allows you to add as many search engines as you want and to position them where you choose. The module's search mechanism is filter-based. Filters form the basis for successful layered navigation. They allow your customers to find products that match their search criteria with a minimum number of clicks.Advanced Search 4 has been developped in order to provide short loading times, even for catalogues containing tens of thousands of products or categories. Initial version published in 2010 - Winner of the Best Modules Awards en 2012 - Listed among the best-selling add-ons since 2010. 3 types of search are available to you:Search your entire catalogue: the search scope covers the entire catalogue.Search within a selection of products: the search scope covers the page the customer is currently visiting.Search by steps: criteria are refined and displayed as your customers specify their search. In addition to its main features, the Advanced Search function is also recognised as one of your best allies when it comes to referencing. It includes an optimised page generator for SEO, which allows you to increase your visibility without any duplicated content! Behind all of these innovations, our objective always remains the same : to help you increase your rate of conversion and boost your sales !As you can imagine, Advanced Search has never been as powerful]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.12.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[229.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/766622-pprod/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/766622-pbig/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Fast & Mass Update]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/fast-mass-updates/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time! In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category. Look for products that you want to add to this category and add them in one click! You also can control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/741974-pprod/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/741974-pbig/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2889]]></id><name><![CDATA[blockyoutubevideos]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Videos - YouTube]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Videos & Music]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Bring your product pages to life&nbsp;on your site and make them interactive by adding videos!  The Product Videos - YouTube module is an ideal way to increase your products&rsquo; conversion rate]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/videos-music/2889-product-videos-youtube.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2889.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Bring your product pages to life&nbsp;on your site and make them interactive by adding videos!  The Product Videos - YouTube module is an ideal way to increase your products&rsquo; conversion rate. It lets you easily and automatically import your YouTube videos and add them wherever you like on your product pages.&nbsp;  &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Videos are an essential tool to make your products more attractive and improve your conversion rate. 73% of consumers are more likely to purchase a product or a service after they&#39;ve watched a video.   This module is an essential tool for your site and your customers: &nbsp;Make your products more attractive by providing your customers with visual and relevant complementary information (features, characteristics, benefits, use, etc.).&nbsp;Increase your conversion rate and reduce product returns. 96% of consumers think it&#39;s easier to reach a decision about an online purchase if they watch a video.&nbsp;Easily enrich your site&#39;s content and improve your natural SEO by adding YouTube videos to your product pages.&nbsp;Improve customer engagement and increase average cart size on your site.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.16]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/625269-pprod/product-videos-youtube.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/625269-pbig/product-videos-youtube.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[bridgeconnector]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Store Manager for PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Third-party Data Integration (CRM, ERP...)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[14-DAY FREE TRIAL! Back office solution you need, to manage your PrestaShop online store efficiently!&nbsp;*** AWARDED AS PRESTASHOP&#39;S FAVORITE IN 2016 ***]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/third-party-data-integrations-crm-erp/2937-store-manager-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[14-DAY FREE TRIAL! Back office solution you need, to manage your PrestaShop online store efficiently!&nbsp;*** AWARDED AS PRESTASHOP&#39;S FAVORITE IN 2016 ***]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you.Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd!&nbsp;Store Manager for PrestaShop is a desktop application, designed to speed up and automate the management of PrestaShop based stores. Not only does it take care of the mass operations with products, categories, orders and customers extending the functionality of the store web back-end, but also lines up with an intuitive interface and advanced addons for easy store management.Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd!&nbsp;Spend an Hour, Save a Day!Store Manager for PrestaShop was designed to work for you and not at the expense of your business. It is your personal assistant that does all the routine tasks, saving you tons of time for greater deeds.For that matter, it provides with ready-made export/import features, report tools, advanced addons, etc. No need to spend a day getting deep into how your store works, spend an hour understanding how Store Manager does the job for you.&nbsp;Take Your Online Business to the BankBuy one Store Manager instead of multiple modules.Use one Store Manager license to manage your multiple stores. Store Manager doesn&rsquo;t require any special skills, so you don&rsquo;t have to pay someone to keep your store database organized. You can implement all the necessary updates yourself with Store Manager for PrestaShop and get on to important tasks.  ​*** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE 2012 ***]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[export]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.19]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[299.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[339.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[269.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/572842-pprod/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/572842-pbig/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3252]]></id><name><![CDATA[printlabels]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Print Labels Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Preparation & Shipping]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With the Print Labels Pro module, save valuable time by automating the preparation of your shipping labels!  This module developed by PrestaShop allows you to prepare, print your delivery labels and s]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/preparation-shipping/3252-print-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/3252.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With the Print Labels Pro module, save valuable time by automating the preparation of your shipping labels!  This module developed by PrestaShop allows you to prepare, print your delivery labels and stick them on the packages for the orders you&#39;re shipping.  You can also choose to print one, two or six labels per page to best match your needs!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time shipping your ordersLower your rate of returned packages due to wrong addresses]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595260-pprod/print-labels.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595260-pbig/print-labels.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4414]]></id><name><![CDATA[allinone_rewards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[All-in-one Rewards: loyalty sponsorship affiliation...]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Referral & Loyalty Programs]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, fa]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/referral-loyalty-programs/4414-all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, facebook and more. Your sales will really increase !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get tons of new customers and increase your brand reputation thanks to the All-in-one Rewards module ! This module allows to set up a complete system of rewards in your shop to increase SEO and reputation thanks to the virality of the system, and to follow very precisely the performance.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[229.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/617761-pprod/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/617761-pbig/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4731]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestablog]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Professional blog]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Blog, Forum & News]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best trafic module on prestashop award 2015. Easy to install and use]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/blog-forum-new/4731-professional-blog.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4731.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best trafic module on prestashop award 2015. Easy to install and use. Fully compatible with every language and will fit perfectly in your template, whether or not multilingual and/or multishop! Optimized for a better SEO.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get in touch with your customers through a blog has become increasingly common for companies who want to build customer loyalty.No need to install a second cms to get all the features you need, this blog is everything you need! Search Engine optimisation (SEO) SEO have been one of the most important part of our developpment on our blog module, It will be a perfect and infallible tool to increase your visibility on the web. Responsive Design Our webdesign team have developped a template who pefectly integrate in all type of template. Responsive or not. Fast support 100% of our customers get an anwser within 1mn to 6 hours maximum (period days worked) to help you as quickly as possible to implement your project.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/730685-pprod/professional-blog.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/730685-pbig/professional-blog.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enhance your PrestaShop SEO  Internal linking is the creation of links between pages of your shop, using keywords you want to achieve a better place on Google.  To optimize the SEO of your website, it is essential to create an internal linking that will allow search engines to browse your shop in the most easy way as possible. The goal is to provide maximum informations with the least clicks deep.  SEO Internal Linking PrestaShop module optimizes the organization of navigation in your store, and plays an essential role in your SEO strategy.  Define the keywords on which you wish to be listed and their landing pages, and let the module create the links for you!  If you want to add automatic links in your categories descriptions, consider installing our PrestaShop module HTML On Descriptions.  Do we really need internal linking?  Internal linking strategy based on specific keywords is an optimization method that has proven its worth. Especially to enhance a content relevance.  Among the disadvantages, you should know that the installation of these links is long and tedious, and requires to follow SEO good practices, to not over-optimize (which would be detected by Google), and must be updated regularly to track changes in your catalog.  With this in mind, we have developed this module, allowing you to deploy thousands of cross links between your pages within minutes, while being sure to observe best practice guidelines of White Hat SEO.  It has been designed to support both SEO agencies and e-shop owners. SEO Internal Linking is really simple to manage.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573343-pprod/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573343-pbig/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sales Reports Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analytics & Statistics]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/analytics-statistics/5255-sales-reports-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[*** WINNER OF THE 2015 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***  Get perfect visibility on your shop's and products' profitability! The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly, profit and profit margin. Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like "what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?". This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed ! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.10.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.4.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963264-pprod/sales-reports-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963264-pbig/sales-reports-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5711]]></id><name><![CDATA[zipcodezone]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shipping fees based on zipcodes]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping Costs]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Apply different shipping fees based on postal codes of your customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-costs/5711-shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/5711.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Apply different shipping fees based on postal codes of your customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With PrestaShop, it is possible to apply different shipping fees based on country or state. However, this does not necessarily represent the reality of carriers. Some will charge higher prices for mountainous or remote areas for example (departments or overseas territories). Improve your shop's shipping system with this module which will allow you to apply different shipping fees based on zip code of your client. Using the zone system of PrestaShop, you will be able to cut a country into as many parts as you want. By department, area or whatever you want. This has the advantage of adapting the way you want your areas. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/650424-pprod/shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/650424-pbig/shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6059]]></id><name><![CDATA[cdiscount]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cdiscount Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplaces]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplaces/6059-cdiscount-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6059.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders. Beneficiate from 3-month subscription free when you register on Cdiscount !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[C Le Marché is one of France’s leading marketplaces.  Boost your sales! Make the most of the traffic generated by Cdiscount to sell your products and enjoy the numerous advantages which make Cdiscount such a success: - payment in 4 instalments (fully supported by Cdiscount) - multiple delivery methods, etc.  Cdiscount takes care of everything! Place your products for sale on the marketplace and manage your orders while Cdiscount takes care of the rest: traffic, easy and secure payment, marketing, etc.  1 single back office! Thanks to the Cdiscount for PrestaShop m